Another technique that competitors like to use to intimidate their opponents is slamming their elbows on the table.
This is no good.
This takes away from your strength.
The shock of your elbow from the table simply takes away from your advantage.
Remember that we're only flesh and blood.
We don't want to smack our elbows onto the table.
It's not going to intimidate anyone.
It never intimidated me.
What we don't want to do is....if Richie gains his advantage as he's coming down on me like this and bends my wrist, I don't want to try and reflex my wrist as far as I can because I'm a hook wrestler.
My wrist likes to be hooked.
So he's got me like this, the best I can do is just hold on until he loses his momentum and then I can start gaining mine back because that's when he's weak.
Otherwise I end up straining my wrist and it's a sure thing that I'll end up losing the match.